export default  [
  {
    "category": "Julien",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which one of these Microsoft subsidiaries doesn't noticeably use Java?",
    "correct_answer": "id Software",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Minecraft",
        "Yammer",
        "LinkedIn"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Julien",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In which language is coded JHipster?",
    "correct_answer": "JavaScript",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Java",
        "Go",
        "Bash"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Julien",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In JavaScript, what is the result of \"0.1+0.2\"?",
    "correct_answer": "0.30000000000000004",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "0.3",
        "0",
        "NaN"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which answer does not correctly describe the new, larger GitHub-hosted runners?",
    "correct_answer": "Java installed by default",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Available for Linux and Windows",
        "Static IP ranges available",
        "Auto-scaled runners by GitHub"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How would you define a set of recommended extensions for a Codespace?",
    "correct_answer": "Configure them in the extensions property of devcontainer.json",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Install them in the dockerfile",
        "Setup a script to install in the dotfiles",
        "Use settings sync to install the specific extensions"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which answer does not correctly describe code scanning in GitHub Advanced Security?",
    "correct_answer": "Third-party tools that output into a CSV format can be integrated with Code Scanning",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Third-party analysis tools can be run, and results imported to GitHub Code Scanning",
      "CodeQL treats code like data, so you can write queries to find patterns in code.",
      "Java is supported by GitHub's code analysis engine, CodeQL"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which Github tool can detect vulnerabilities in the dependencies of your Github repository?",
    "correct_answer": "Dependabot",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Github copilot",
        "Github scanning",
        "Vulneracheck",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Github Artifacts?",
    "correct_answer": "A way to store data produced by a workflow",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A cloud storage solution from Github",
        "A place to store source code",
        "A solution for an open issue",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Github Actions?",
    "correct_answer": "A platform that allows you to automate CI/CD (Build, Test, Deployment), and react to other GitHub events.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A bot that helps you improve your DevOps Automation",
        "A tool that helps you take action on security issues inside your codebase.",
        "An AI pair programmer",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What tool can help you create a quick and consistent development environment?",
    "correct_answer": "GitHub Codespaces",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "GitHub Copilot",
        "GitHub Actions",
        "GitHub Container Registry",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "GitHub secret scanning is available",
    "correct_answer": "on private repos with GitHub Advanced Security and public repos on github.com",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Only private repos on github.com",
        "GitHub Enterprise Server",
        "Only public repos on github.com"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Is it possible to create a GitHub Action workflow which reacts to GitHub Issue events (e.g. opened, new comment, closed)?",
    "correct_answer": "Yes",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "No",
        "Only on GitHub Enterprise Cloud",
        "Only with GitHub-hosted runners"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is InnerSource?",
    "correct_answer": "Bringing Open Source Practices to our internal development (e.g. removing silos)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "An early phase of Open Source Adoption",
        "When code is locked down to the teams that need it",
        "A program used to build an Open Source community internally (e.g. drive usage adoption in a secure way, encourage contributions, recognition for OSS work among employees, etc.)"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is an Open Source Program Office?",
    "correct_answer": "A program used to build an Open Source community internally (e.g. drive usage adoption in a secure way, encourage contributions, recognition for OSS work among employees, etc.)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "An early phase of Open Source Adoption",
        "Bringing Open Source Practices to our internal development (e.g. removing silos)",
        "When code is locked down to the teams that need it"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is the device posture API used for?",
    "correct_answer": "To detect foldable devices screens angle",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "To monitor user's posture to avoid back pain",
        "To detect dropping devices to flush caches and prevent data loss",
        "To detect if front or back camera is used"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What was the first mainstream foldable multi-screen device?",
    "correct_answer": "Nintendo Game & Watch",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Surface Duo",
        "Galaxy Fold",
        "LG G8X ThinQ"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What CSS feature is used to create responsive designs?",
    "correct_answer": "Media queries",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Selectors",
        "Flex box",
        "Sass"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What can be used to reduce data access latency in a distributed app?",
    "correct_answer": "Cache",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Database",
        "Queue",
        "An Intel Pentium processor"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What's the main language used to develop the Microsoft Teams app?",
    "correct_answer": "JavaScript",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Java",
        "C#",
        "C++"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Azure Spring Apps?",
    "correct_answer": "Managed service for hosting Spring Apps",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A service to deploy only a single Spring Boot app",
        "A new Spring framework",
        "A new IaaS solution for hosting Spring Apps"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which one(s) of these Azure solutions can you use to deploy Spring Boot App?",
    "correct_answer": "All the answers",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Azure Spring Apps",
        "Azure App Service",
        "Azure Container Apps"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which one(s) of these Azure solutions can you use to deploy Spring Cloud Apps?",
    "correct_answer": "Azure Spring Apps",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Azure Spring Cloud",
        "Azure Spring Framework",
        "All the answers"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which one(s) of these Azure solutions can you use to deploy containers?",
    "correct_answer": "All the answers",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Azure Container Instances",
        "Azure Kubernetes Service",
        "Azure Container Apps"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which one(s) of these  App Servers is/are supported by App Service?",
    "correct_answer": "Tomcat and Jboss EAP",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tomcat and Weblogic",
        "Weblogic and JBoss EAP",
        "WebSphere and Tomcat"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which Azure Messaging solution supports JMS?",
    "correct_answer": "Azure Service Bus",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Azure Event Grid",
        "Azure Event Hub",
        "Azure Queue Storage"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which GitHub Action configures Java on a GitHub runner?",
    "correct_answer": "actions/setup-java",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "actions/initialise-java",
        "actions/configure-java",
        "actions/java-setup"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Github Artifacts?",
    "correct_answer": "A way to store data produced by a workflow",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A cloud storage solution from Github",
        "A place to store source code",
        "A change request to your code base"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which Microsoft product helps developers starting a new project quickly and efficiently?",
    "correct_answer": "Azure Dev Box",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Azure Virtual Desktop",
        "Windows 365",
        "Visual Workshop"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which editor integrates with Azure",
    "correct_answer": "IntelliJ",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "vim",
        "nano",
        "notepad++"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is an octopus merge?",
    "correct_answer": "It takes two or more branches and merge them in a single branch",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "It stages several commits and merges them at once",
        "It's a type of octopus living in the atlantic ocean",
        "It's a merge done with Git Kraken"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is a protected branch in Github?",
    "correct_answer": "A branch which you must meet certain standards to be able to commit to it",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A secured branch which only accepts perfect code",
        "A hidden branch, and only available for specific users or groups",
        "A branch used to work on security features"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Why would you create a pull request?",
    "correct_answer": "To ask colleagues/community for code review before merging",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "To pull code from a repository",
        "To ask colleagues/community for help",
        "To contact Microsoft support"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How many Azure components do you need to create an approval flow using Java?",
    "correct_answer": "1",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "4"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What was Github copilot trained on?",
    "correct_answer": "Public GitHub repositories",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Private GitHub repositories",
        "Windows repository",
        "Stackoverflow"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What Azure service is supporting the newest Forza Horizon 5?",
    "correct_answer": "Azure Kubernetes Services",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Azure Virtual Machines",
        "Azure Container Apps",
        "Azure SQL"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What does IaaS mean?",
    "correct_answer": "Infrastructure as a Service",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Interopability as a Service",
        "Integration as a Service",
        "Instances a Service"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What does SaaS mean?",
    "correct_answer": "Software as a Service",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Solution as a Service",
        "Security as a Service",
        "Selling as a Service"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What does PaaS mean?",
    "correct_answer": "Platform as a Service",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Programming as a Service",
        "Pentesting as a Service",
        "Preaching as a Service"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is the smallest vCPU you can choose for a Spring App in Azure Spring Apps?",
    "correct_answer": "0.5",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "4"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Can you get started for free with Microsoft Azure?",
    "correct_answer": "Yes, everyone can with the free tier",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "No you can't",
        "Only if you are a student",
        "Yes if you are a .NET developer"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How can you start using Microsoft Azure?",
    "correct_answer": "All of them",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Credit Card",
        "Free trial",
        "Promo code"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Who is the biggest Open Source contributor?",
    "correct_answer": "Microsoft",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Google",
        "AWS",
        "Redhat"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Behind .NET, what is the second most watched topic on Microsoft Docs?",
    "correct_answer": "Java",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Golang",
        "PHP",
        "NodeJS"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Virtual Machine scale sets?",
    "correct_answer": "A set of virtual machines that can scale to help you meet demand",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A queuing system used for requests to a virtual machine",
        "A service to scale Java Apps",
        "A set of exact same virtual machines that can scale to help you meet demand"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How can you scale Azure VM?",
    "correct_answer": "Using Virtual Machine Scale Sets",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Using availability sets",
        "Using Azure Disaster Recovery",
        "Using replica sets"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is the entry cost of App Service?",
    "correct_answer": "It's free",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "It's free for Linux and 4.99€/month for Windows",
        "It's free for Windows and 4.99€/month for Linux",
        "It's 4.99€/month"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which service checks vulnarabilities in Azure Container Registry?",
    "correct_answer": "Microsoft Defender for Containers",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Microsoft Security Suite",
        "Azure Cybersecurity Program",
        "Microsoft Anti-Spyware"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is the App Service SLA (Service Level Agreement)?",
    "correct_answer": "99.95%",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "99.99%",
        "99.90%",
        "99%"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What was the codename for the Azure project, 15 years back?",
    "correct_answer": "Red Dog",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "MCS",
        "Copper",
        "Zune"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which of the following Java class types provides generic CRUD methods to manage JPA objects?",
    "correct_answer": "Repository",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Controller",
        "Entity",
        "Interface"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is NSG?",
    "correct_answer": "Network Security Group (A way to filter traffic)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Native Security Guard (A native service to enforce security in Azure)",
        "National Security Gate (A Belgium-Microsoft Security program)",
        "National System for Geospatial-Intelligence "
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "By when will Microsoft's datacenters be 100% running on renewable energy?",
    "correct_answer": "2025",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2023",
        "2027",
        "2030"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Where will the three Availability Zones of the new Belgian Azure datacentre come?",
    "correct_answer": "We don't even know ourselves",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Zaventem",
        "Ghent",
        "Wavre"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is not a goal of the Cloud for Sustainability cloud?",
    "correct_answer": "A marketing campaign to replace plastic straws in the Microsoft cafeterias",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Build a sustaniable IT infrastructure",
        "Reduce the environmental impact of operations",
        "Create sustainable value chains"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What does ABC stand for?",
    "correct_answer": "Azure Belgian Central (the new upcoming Azure region in Belgium!)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Always Be Concerned (The mindset of assuming breach by default)",
        "American Broadcasting Corporation",
        "Artificial Bee Colony algorithm (a search algorithm)"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How can you create resources in Azure?",
    "correct_answer": "All of them and many more…",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Azure CLI",
        "Terraform",
        "Azure portal"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is AKS?",
    "correct_answer": "Azure Kubernetes Services",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Azure Koffie Service",
        "Azure Kontainer Service",
        "Azure Kudo Service"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Where can I deploy my Maven-packaged Spring Boot application?",
    "correct_answer": "All off above",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "App Service",
        "VM",
        "Spring Cloud"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which service allows developers to scaffold the structure of a Spring Boot application?",
    "correct_answer": "Spring Initializr",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Maven",
        "The Azure CLI",
        "Proxer"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which Azure service is written in Java?",
    "correct_answer": "HDInsight",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Internal Control Systems",
        "Databricks",
        "All of them"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is the Digital AmBEtion Plan?",
    "correct_answer": "A plan to make every Belgian enterprise on this planet a digital company",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The new datacenter in Belgium",
        "2Education everyone to become digital015"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which managed solution can you use for caching on Azure?",
    "correct_answer": "Azure Redis Cache013",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Redis on AKS",
        "Logstash",
        "Memcache"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is the group id of Azure SDK?",
    "correct_answer": "com.azure",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "com.microsoft.azure",
        "com.azurewebs",
        "com.microsoft"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is the license of Java binaries of the Microsoft Build of OpenJDK?",
    "correct_answer": "GPLv2",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Apache 2.0",
        "MIT",
        "Commercial License"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What are the correct lyrics for 'Java Life' rap music?",
    "correct_answer": "We sweat hard in these cubicles",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "We work hard in these cubicles",
        "We code hard in these cubicles",
        "We sleep hard in these cubicles"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "When Devoxx was initiated for the first time?",
    "correct_answer": "2001",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1999",
        "2000",
        "2002"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What was the formerly name of Devoxx?",
    "correct_answer": "Javapolis",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Belgian Java User Group",
        "Javaconf",
        "BeJava"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which XBOX Game Studios' game is implemented in Java?",
    "correct_answer": "Minecraft",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Halo",
        "Forza Horizon",
        "Age of Empire"
      ]
  }
]